[Music]
previously on bro dependent since I'm
over your place all the time anyway
maybe I could like bring some stuff over
or you could just put an overnight bag
in your car oh yeah yeah that's a great
idea too what is this my resume it's
five words in a deck yeah I drew that I
got my eyesight back and I can see
things clearer than ever the end can I
go now that was quite good Zach oh
did I get
it
sexy that's very good yes keep
going keep going oh yes yes that's yummy
we are in the Yum Zone I love this oh my
God you guys are too good at this you're
too good Dane two seconds let's have you
step out let's do a couple with Zach and
Lexi God bless great work everybody
great work are you for real dude
we've been doing this for like 15
minutes okay you got somewhere else you
want to be yeah anywhere hi hi God you
look hot out there okay let's um let's
do some couple photos let's let's have a
little affection this one let's do some
arms around the shoulders oh no no no no
dude I can't do that sorry why because
dude I'm in a committed ass relationship
she's right there hey Carolyn yeah I
love you a see no can do dude can't be
in here no I'm sorry I'm so sorry Martin
he just burst in there was nothing I do
J we get it you can do an Austin Powers
impression Zach listen um something huge
happened cool story no no I haven't I
haven't told the story yet Marissa get
them off of my set I'm sorry you have to
leave you're disrupting the shoot oh
yeah she does sound like Austin Powers
Yeah Baby do I make you honey baby
swing one million
dollar uh Foxy
Cleopatra serious like that was like
much my first Direction was like young
Beyonce as Foxy Cleopatra get it I was
like oh I'm a man now thank you can we
like talk dude fine let's just go over
there this chick is like obsessed with
me oh
weird dude I I had this kind of like big
interview with lids the other day and I
kind of blew it dude dude that'd be
perfect for you you love hats I know
dude I was so bummed I like went home
and just treated myself to a consolation
bong but even that like didn't work work
out for me you know like I got all
panicky and I was just like Anderson
it's not your day just switch over to
oxycotton smart yeah dude and it was
great cuz like I couldn't feel anything
but the thing about oxy is it makes me
feel so sluggish you know so I like slam
through those energy drinks have you
tried Quattro crazy oh my god dude I
love those oh yeah it's the dude
yeah dude banana bananza you have an
excellent body oh bless you get your
hands on it so good so anyway it was
working out cuz like I was like
perfectly numb but also jacked as
and then my brain was just like
sell this and then dude like just like
my hands without my brain Drew
this Quattro
cotton holy dude I know dude Zach
seriously let's just get this over with
oh yeah you're right all right no more
photos everybody thank you so much good
day guys really good work no no you're
not done ex excuse me this is
your job you can't just leave hey Zach
who am I blah blah blah blah blah I have
a camera blah blah blah blah blah my
dick is a tiny camera you're that dude
I'm that guy is your dick a tiny camera
what what what what what what what what
what what click click you
guys he's so mad dude that was funny as
dude yeah dude thanks hey dude I've
missed this yeah me
too hey do you like sex yeah let's go
have some so um what do you say man you
want to get into bed with Quattro cotton
no dude I mean I'd rather just be
business partners oh yeah no that's even
better yeah dude nice let's get out of
here all right
Carolyn hey Carolyn it's
weird it's fine dude we can just take
my I don't know how I got here this
stuff really works man like I have no
idea how I got
[Laughter]
[Music]
here heyy uh thanks for watching Pro
dependent on comedy Central's YouTube
channel best episode ever uh yeah like
comment and subscribe and check out more
on comedy.com and do we're back we're
back we're
like